听译: 小咩    监制: J
微博搜索: 果仁字幕组    招募QQ群: 485275135
粉丝互动
官方QQ群: 189796106
认识这个人么
Do you know this one?
黛比 海洋
Debbie Ocean.
重罪犯
Convicted Felon.
她兄弟 丹尼 海洋
Her brother Danny Ocean.
更是个重罪犯
More convicted felon.
她曾出现在案发现场
She was present on the night of the incident
哇塞 所以嘞
Wooo.  So.....
给你们介绍下这个假设的情景
We would like to present you all with a hypothetical situation.
有多假设
How hypothetical ?
也还好 除非我们搞砸了
Not very, unless we screw up.
它叫做斗山
It's called the Doosan
上面有超过六磅的钻石
It's over 6 pounds of diamonds
价值超过一个亿美金
Value that  are over 100 million dollars
其实是一亿五千万
150 million actually, hahahhahaha
现在我们要把它抢过来
Now we are going to rob it.
棒
Sweet
开心啊见到你 你看起来
Great to see you. You you look...
最近蹲号子了？
Recently incarcerating?
太赞了
That was spectacular.
这些黑客都是俄国佬
These are all Russians, they are hackers.
有不是黑客的俄国佬么
Are there no hackers weren't Russian?
我们街区就没有俄国佬
No, there's barely any Russian to our own arcades.
你要我安排个会么
Do you want me to set up a meeting
当然
YES
做好七件珠宝要多久
How long would it take you to make 7 pieces of jewellery？
五六个小时
5 or 6 hour.
那我让你不要跟你妈住在一起又有多久了
How long if I told you didn't have to live with your mother anymore
这就是你为啥没老公
没多久
Less
怎么可能会有人资历过高  毕竟这可是
Can anyone really be overqualified. This is the Mac Gayla.
麦克Gay拉
after
盖拉 麦克盖拉
Gala, the Mac Gala.
是是是 盖拉
The Gala, yeah.
好 看好啦
Alright, here we go.
不要闭眼 不要眨眼
Don't sleep, don't sleep.
她一下就会消失 走啦
Cause she might disappear. Zou na
我们可以黑进麦克安保系统
We could just .... hack the Mac security system?
嘿 蠢货
Hey, fool!
可怜的家伙
You poor thing.
我要进监狱了 我会无聊死的
I'm going to prison and I'm going to be really really bored.
没必要
Not necessarily.
条子来了
Police coming.
我要撤了
I need to go.
游戏开始
Game on.
嗨瞧你这表情
Hey bluesteel.
注：bluesteel源自电影超级名模 后指很吃惊的表情
我天 这些人真是不能相信
Man they are just not trust worthy.
看路
Watch?
怎么了
What's happening?
该死的信号
Can't get a signal.
等等等等 等
Wait. wait. wa.....it...wait.
你每次移动得从这儿开始
Every time you move you have to start from some...
你干了啥
What did you / what did she do?
把它打开啊
To turn it on.
噢
Oh~